{
    "subject": "resource/Freiburg_im_Breisgau",
    "predicate": "property/sepLowC",
    "object": "11.7",
    "human_readable": "The latitude of Freiburg im Breisgau is 11.7.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9410861730575562,
            "question": "What is the latitude of Freiburg im Breisgau?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7756503820419312,
            "question": "Are there any other cities with a similar latitude to Freiburg im Breisgau?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7155646085739136,
            "question": "Where is Freiburg im Breisgau located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6475380659103394,
            "question": "How would you describe the geographical position of Freiburg im Breisgau?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6352192759513855,
            "question": "Is Freiburg im Breisgau in the northern or southern hemisphere?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5754457116127014,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about Freiburg im Breisgau?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5394254326820374,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Freiburg im Breisgau?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5256050825119019,
            "question": "Can you find any famous landmarks in Freiburg im Breisgau?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31061169505119324,
            "question": "What is the significance of latitude?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1851073056459427,
            "question": "How does the latitude of a city affect its weather patterns?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The latitude of Freiburg im Breisgau is 11.7.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6006_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of latitude?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6006_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you find any famous landmarks in Freiburg im Breisgau?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6006_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the climate like in Freiburg im Breisgau?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6006_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6006_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6006_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6006_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6006_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6006_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6006_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6006_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6006_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6006_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6006_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here's the evaluation of the triple \"The latitude of Freiburg im Breisgau is 11.7\":\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because none of the documents mention a latitude of 11.7 for Freiburg im Breisgau. The correct latitude and longitude are mentioned in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6006/re-ranker-msmarco/75.txt, which is 47.9959 and 7.85222, respectively."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the documents, the latitude of Freiburg im Breisgau is 47.995609, not 11.7. The provided information supports that Freiburg im Breisgau has a latitude and longitude of 47.995609 and 7.852736 respectively."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}